{
    "subject": "resource/24_Hour_Party_People",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Andy_Serkis",
    "human_readable": "The movie 24 Hour Party People stars Andy Serkis.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.965938150882721,
            "question": "Has Andy Serkis starred in other films besides 24 Hour Party People?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8619263172149658,
            "question": "Who stars in the movie 24 Hour Party People?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8087366819381714,
            "question": "Name an actor who has appeared in 24 Hour Party People."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7675507068634033,
            "question": "What kind of movie is 24 Hour Party People?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7280294299125671,
            "question": "Who directed the movie 24 Hour Party People?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.683826744556427,
            "question": "In what film does Andy Serkis have a role?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6225321292877197,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie that Andy Serkis appears in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6183643937110901,
            "question": "Are there any famous movies featuring Andy Serkis?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6145755052566528,
            "question": "What year was the movie 24 Hour Party People released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5690791606903076,
            "question": "Is Andy Serkis known for his acting roles?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The movie 24 Hour Party People stars Andy Serkis.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7278_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the movie 24 Hour Party People released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7278_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any famous movies featuring Andy Serkis?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7278_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the movie that Andy Serkis appears in?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7278_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7278_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7278_108.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7278_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7278_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7278_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7278_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7278_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7278_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7278_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7278_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Andy Serkis played the role of Martin Hannett in the film \"24 Hour Party People,\" which directly supports the statement that the movie \"24 Hour Party People\" stars Andy Serkis."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}